Kritik Jambusariya

Greeting,

I have been a Web Developer for the past 1 year. I have invested all my time in learning Web Development and built multiple projects. You may check them out on my GitHub link provided(last link in project section). I am very intrigued by this industry. I want to learn new things/technologies constantly. I'm very open to work in different ways and styles. Looking to gain some professional experience.



Vasant Nagari, Vasai East, Vasai-Virar, Maharashtra, India





Contact Info

Email: Kritikjambusariya@gmail.com

Phone: +91 73500 52692

Skills

- · React JS
- Redux
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB
- Express
- Python
- Node.js / Express.js
- HTML + CSS
- Hosting
- · Debugging Code
- Researching
- Troubleshooting

Languages

- English Fluent
- French Beginner

Major Projects

E-commerce website

Built using MERN Stack

https://ishopecomm.netlify.app

Vector-Art Website

https://vectorart.netlify.app

Online Assessment

MCQ app with login and register functionality using MERN Stack

https://onlineassessment.netlify.app

Blog app

Full Stack blog app

https://sirenblog.netlify.app

Additional Projects

- To-do Application using JavaScript (https://github.com/Kritik69/Assignment4)
- Online Ticket Maker (live Website: https://ticketgenerator.netlify.app/)
- Card Maker (live Website: https://cardsgenerator.netlify.app/)
- Out of Office mail generator (live Website: https://ooogenerator.netlify.app/)
- Smart Toll using Visible Light Interface on STM32
- MCAworldwide (live Website: https://mcaworldwide.netlify.app/ or https://mcaworldwide.in/)
- Next Js (https://github.com/Kritik69/NextJsPrj)
- Many more projects (https://github.com/Kritik69)

Work Experience

June 2022 - July 2022



Web Developer Intern

V-ART Services

Interned for V-Art as a Web developer, mostly working with React JS. Website built at V-Art

- 1: https://mcaworldwide.in/
- 2: https://vectorart.netlify.app/

March 2022 - April 2022



Web Developer Intern BotX

Interned for BotX Automation as a Web developer Online Ticket Maker and Card Maker projects mentioned above in the list were made for

BotX Automation. These websites were built using Basic JAVASCRIPT.

Education



2019 - 2023

Shah & Anchor Kutchhi Engineering College Electronics and Telecommunication

Certifications

- Full-Stack developer from <u>Prepbytes.com</u> (certificate link:

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bPl3bVbGlfvK1B81H3fefJNyJ1EE22R0/view)

- Python from Udemy (certificate link: https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-0c58122b-ed46-40a9-a57d-f978c5606534/)